A Guide to the Commonwealth Fund records, Mental Hygiene Program, SG 1, Series 25 FA297
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Special Studies, 1929-1952; 4; 9 box(es)
  - National Committee for Mental Hygiene - Study of Psychiatric Education - Reports, 1934 (Box 19, Folder 282)
  - National Committee for Mental Hygiene - Study of Psychiatric Education - Reports, 1934 (Box 19, Folder 283)
  - New York City Committee on Mental Hygiene - Psychiatric War Emergency Study Unit - General Files and Correspondence, 1943-1945 (Box 19, Folder 284)
  - New York City Committee on Mental Hygiene - Psychiatric War Emergency Study Unit - General Files and Correspondence, 1943-1945 (Box 19, Folder 285)
  - New York Hospital Payne Whitney Clinic - Psychiatric War Emergency Special Treatment Clinic - General Files and Correspondence, 1943-1947 (Box 19, Folder 286)
  - New York Hospital Payne Whitney Clinic - Psychiatric War Emergency Special Treatment Clinic - General Files and Correspondence, 1943-1947 (Box 19, Folder 287)
  - New York Hospital Payne Whitney Clinic - Psychiatric War Emergency Special Treatment Clinic - General Files and Correspondence, 1943-1947 (Box 19, Folder 288)
  - Peter Bent Brigham Hospital - Psychiatric and Neurologic Service - General Files and Correspondence, 1941-1943 (Box 19, Folder 289)
  - Peter Bent Brigham Hospital - Psychiatric and Neurologic Service - General Files and Correspondence, 1941-1943 (Box 19, Folder 290)
  - Psychiatric Research Material - General Data - Correspondence, 1938-1939 (Box 19, Folder 291)
  - Psychiatric Research Material - General Data - Memoranda, May-December; 1938 (Box 19, Folder 292)
  - Ryan, W. Carson, Jr. - Study - Practical Application of Mental Hygiene in the Schools - General Files and Correspondence, 1935-1938 (Box 19, Folder 293)
  - Smith College School for Social Work - Staff Salaries - General Files and Correspondence, 1933-1934 (Box 19, Folder 294)
  - Society of the New York Hospital - Pediatric-Psychiatric Service - Dr. Norvelle C. LaMar - General Files and Correspondence, 1933-1938 (Box 19, Folder 295)
  - Society of the New York Hospital - Pediatric-Psychiatric Service - Dr. Norvelle C. LaMar - General Files and Correspondence, 1933-1938 (Box 19, Folder 296)
  - Society of the New York Hospital - Pediatric-Psychiatric Service - Dr. Norvelle C. LaMar - General Files and Correspondence, 1933-1938 (Box 19, Folder 297)
  - Society of the New York Hospital - Pediatric-Psychiatric Service - Dr. Norvelle C. LaMar - General Files and Correspondence, 1933-1938 (Box 19, Folder 298)
  - Society of the New York Hospital - Pediatric-Psychiatric Service - Dr. Norvelle C. LaMar - General Files and Correspondence, 1933-1938 (Box 19, Folder 299)
  - Society of the New York Hospital - Pediatric-Psychiatric Service - Dr. Norvelle C. LaMar - General Files and Correspondence, 1939-1943 (Box 20, Folder 300)
  - Society of the New York Hospital - Pediatric-Psychiatric Service - Dr. Norvelle C. LaMar - General Files and Correspondence, 1939-1943 (Box 20, Folder 301)
  - Society of the New York Hospital - Pediatric-Psychiatric Service - Dr. Norvelle C. LaMar - General Files and Correspondence, 1939-1943 (Box 20, Folder 302)
  - Stanford University - Pediatric-Psychiatric Unit - Financial Data, 1939-1947 (Box 20, Folder 303)
  - Stanford University - Pediatric-Psychiatric Unit - Financial Data, 1939-1947 (Box 20, Folder 304)
  - Stanford University - Pediatric-Psychiatric Unit - Financial Data, 1939-1947 (Box 20, Folder 305)
  - Stanford University - Pediatric-Psychiatric Unit - Financial Data, 1939-1947 (Box 20, Folder 306)
  - Stanford University - Pediatric-Psychiatric Unit - General Files and Correspondence, 1938-1950 (Box 20, Folder 307)
  - Stanford University - Pediatric-Psychiatric Unit - General Files and Correspondence, 1938-1950 (Box 20, Folder 308)
  - Stanford University - Pediatric-Psychiatric Unit - General Files and Correspondence, 1938-1950 (Box 20, Folder 309)
  - Stanford University - Pediatric-Psychiatric Unit - General Files and Correspondence, 1938-1950 (Box 20, Folder 310)
  - Stanford University - Pediatric-Psychiatric Unit - General Files and Correspondence, 1938-1950 (Box 20, Folder 311)
  - Stanford University - Pediatric-Psychiatric Unit - General Files and Correspondence, 1938-1950 (Box 20, Folder 312)
  - Stanford University - Pediatric-Psychiatric Unit - General Files and Correspondence, 1938-1950 (Box 20, Folder 313)
  - Stanford University - Pediatric-Psychiatric Unit - General Files and Correspondence, 1938-1950 (Box 20, Folder 314)
  - Stanford University - Pediatric-Psychiatric Unit - General Files and Correspondence, 1938-1950 (Box 20, Folder 315)
  - Stanford University - Pediatric-Psychiatric Unit - General Files and Correspondence, 1938-1950 (Box 20, Folder 316)
  - Stanford University - Pediatric-Psychiatric Unit - General Files and Correspondence, 1938-1950 (Box 20, Folder 317)
  - Union Theological Seminary - General Files and Correspondence, 1929-1950 (Box 21, Folder 318)
  - University of California - Child Psychiatry Unit - Financial Data, 1942-1949 (Box 21, Folder 319)
  - University of California - Child Psychiatry Unit - Financial Data, 1942-1949 (Box 21, Folder 320)
  - University of California - Child Psychiatry Unit - General Files and Correspondence, 1937-1949 (Box 21, Folder 321)
  - University of California - Child Psychiatry Unit - General Files and Correspondence, 1937-1949 (Box 21, Folder 322)
  - University of California - Child Psychiatry Unit - General Files and Correspondence, 1937-1949 (Box 21, Folder 323)
  - University of California - Child Psychiatry Unit - General Files and Correspondence, 1937-1949 (Box 21, Folder 324)
  - University of California - Child Psychiatry Unit - General Files and Correspondence, 1937-1949 (Box 21, Folder 325)
  - University of California - Child Psychiatry Unit - General Files and Correspondence, 1937-1949 (Box 21, Folder 326)
  - University of California - Child Psychiatry Unit - General Files and Correspondence, 1937-1949 (Box 21, Folder 327)
  - University of California - Child Psychiatry Unit - General Files and Correspondence, 1937-1949 (Box 21, Folder 328)
  - University of California - Mental Health Service in Pediatrics - Dr. Schade - Financial Data, 1947-1952 (Box 21, Folder 329)
  - University of California - Mental Health Service in Pediatrics - Dr. Schade - General Files and Correspondence, 1947-1951 (Box 21, Folder 330)
  - University of Cincinnati - Department of Pediatrics - Mental Health Unit - General Files and Correspondence, 1943-1951 (Box 21, Folder 331)
  - University of Cincinnati - Department of Psychiatry - Psychiatric Liaison Service in Medicine - General Files and Correspondence, 1942-1946 (Box 21, Folder 332)
  - University of Cincinnati - Department of Psychiatry - Psychiatric Liaison Service in Medicine - General Files and Correspondence, 1942-1946 (Box 21, Folder 333)
  - University of Cincinnati - Department of Psychiatry - Psychiatric Liaison Service in Medicine - General Files and Correspondence, 1946-1950 (Box 22, Folder 334)
  - University of Cincinnati - Department of Psychiatry - Psychiatric Liaison Service in Medicine - General Files and Correspondence, 1946-1950 (Box 22, Folder 335)
  - University of Cincinnati - Department of Psychiatry - Psychiatric Liaison Service in Medicine - General Files and Correspondence, 1946-1950 (Box 22, Folder 336)
  - University of Louisville - Department of Psychiatry - Financial Data, 1937-1943 (Box 22, Folder 337)
  - University of Louisville - Department of Psychiatry - Financial Data, 1937-1943 (Box 22, Folder 338)
  - University of Louisville - Department of Psychiatry - General Files and Correspondence, 1935-1941 (Box 22, Folder 339)
  - University of Louisville - Department of Psychiatry - General Files and Correspondence, 1935-1941 (Box 22, Folder 340)
  - University of Louisville - Department of Psychiatry - General Files and Correspondence, 1935-1941 (Box 22, Folder 341)
  - University of Louisville - Department of Psychiatry - General Files and Correspondence, 1935-1941 (Box 22, Folder 342)
  - University of Louisville - Department of Psychiatry - General Files and Correspondence, 1935-1941 (Box 22, Folder 343)
  - University of Louisville - Department of Psychiatry - General Files and Correspondence, 1935-1941 (Box 22, Folder 344)
  - University of Louisville - Department of Psychiatry - General Files and Correspondence, 1935-1941 (Box 22, Folder 345)
  - University of Louisville - Department of Psychiatry - General Files and Correspondence, 1941-1948 (Box 23, Folder 346)
  - University of Louisville - Department of Psychiatry - General Files and Correspondence, 1941-1948 (Box 23, Folder 347)
  - University of Louisville - Department of Psychiatry - General Files and Correspondence, 1941-1948 (Box 23, Folder 348)
  - University of Louisville - Department of Psychiatry - General Files and Correspondence, 1941-1948 (Box 23, Folder 349)
  - University of Louisville - Department of Psychiatry - Teaching Material, 1938-1941 (Box 23, Folder 350)
  - University of Louisville - Department of Psychiatry - Teaching Material, 1938-1941 (Box 23, Folder 351)
  - University of Louisville - Department of Psychiatry - Teaching Material, 1938-1941 (Box 23, Folder 352)
  - University of Louisville - Department of Psychiatry - Teaching Material, 1938-1941 (Box 23, Folder 353)
  - University of Minnesota - Psychiatry and Child Guidance - Financial Data, 1938-1944 (Box 23, Folder 354)
  - University of Minnesota - Psychiatry and Child Guidance - Financial Data, 1938-1944 (Box 23, Folder 355)
  - University of Minnesota - Psychiatry and Child Guidance - Financial Data, 1938-1944 (Box 23, Folder 356)
  - University of Minnesota - Psychiatry and Child Guidance - Financial Data, 1938-1944 (Box 23, Folder 357)
  - University of Minnesota - Psychiatry and Child Guidance - General Files and Correspondence, 1937-1947 (Box 24, Folder 358)
  - University of Minnesota - Psychiatry and Child Guidance - General Files and Correspondence, 1937-1947 (Box 24, Folder 359)
  - University of Minnesota - Psychiatry and Child Guidance - General Files and Correspondence, 1937-1947 (Box 24, Folder 360)
  - University of Minnesota - Psychiatry and Child Guidance - General Files and Correspondence, 1937-1947 (Box 24, Folder 361)
  - University of Minnesota - Psychiatry and Child Guidance - General Files and Correspondence, 1937-1947 (Box 24, Folder 362)
  - University of Minnesota - Psychiatry and Child Guidance - General Files and Correspondence, 1937-1947 (Box 24, Folder 363)
  - University of Minnesota - Psychiatry and Child Guidance - General Files and Correspondence, 1937-1947 (Box 24, Folder 364)
  - University of Minnesota - Psychiatry and Child Guidance - General Files and Correspondence, 1937-1947 (Box 24, Folder 365)
  - University of Minnesota - Psychiatry and Child Guidance - General Files and Correspondence, 1937-1947 (Box 24, Folder 366)
  - University of Minnesota - Psychiatry and Child Guidance - General Files and Correspondence, 1937-1947 (Box 24, Folder 367)
  - University of Minnesota - Psychiatry and Child Guidance - General Files and Correspondence, 1937-1947 (Box 24, Folder 368)
  - University of Minnesota - Psychiatry and Child Guidance - General Files and Correspondence, 1937-1947 (Box 24, Folder 369)
  - University of Minnesota - Psychiatry and Child Guidance - Teaching Material, 1940-1944 (Box 24, Folder 370)
  - Vanderbilt University - Department of Pediatrics, Mental Health Service - General Files and Correspondence, 1939-1946 (Box 24, Folder 371)